Guide to the Stanford University, Bookstore, Audit Materials
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Bookstore, audit materials
1992-1993
SC0492
Stanford Bookstore.
1 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Access Terms
Stanford Bookstore. Audit Committee; Stanford Bookstore.; Stansky, Peter, 1932-
Collection Contents
- Audit materials, 1992-1993
  - Background Investigative Materials, 1992 Apr 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Audit Committee to the Board of Directors, 1992 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Second Preliminary Report on Summary of Analysis and Findings and Accountants' Report thereon., 1993 Jul 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Second Report on Agreed-Upon Procedures (Binder one of two), 1993 Aug 24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Second Report on Agreed-Upon Procedures (Binder two of two), 1993 Aug 24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Audit Committee to the Board of Directors, 1992 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Bookstore Audit info, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Bookstore Budget and Audit info, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Bookstore Board of Directors info, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - More audit info, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)